A Guide to Governor Lawrence Douglas Wilder Scheduling Office Records, 1989-1994
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Governor L. Douglas Wilder Scheduling Office Records, 1989-1994
The Library of Virginia
35539, 34185
17.5 cu. ft.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Transferred from Governor L. Douglas Wilder on 21 May 1992 and 31 October 1996.
Biographical Information
The Scheduling Office schedules the Governor's time. The Scheduling Director assembles all scheduling requests, corresponds with those who seek appointments, consults the Governor's Counselor, representatives from the Communications and Policy offices, and then makes scheduling commitments for the Governor. The Scheduling Office compiles complete background packets for meetings and event forms. Jacqueline M. Fritz and Lyn C. Cornish were Directors of Scheduling during Governor Lawrence Douglas Wilder's administration (1990-1994).
Scope and Content
Records, 1989-1994, of the Scheduling Office during the administration of Governor Lawrence Douglas Wilder. The collection is housed in 50 boxes and includes appointments, articles, brochures, correspondence, invitations and regrets, newspaper clippings, photographs, requests for interviews, and schedules. The bulk of the collections consists of invitations to the Governor from individuals, institutions, and political and civic groups.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged alphabetically by folder title.
Contents List
- Appointments--Cancelled, 1990-1991. (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Appointments--Cancelled, 1990-1991. (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Appointments--Cancelled, 1990-1991. (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Appointment Requests--Accepted December, 1989. (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Appointment Requests--Declined December, 1989. (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Appointment Requests--Declined January, 1990. (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Aviation Billing, 1990-1994. (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Beyer, Donald--Lt. Governor, 1990-1991. (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Budget--Miscellaneous, 1990. (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Comments, 1990-1993. (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Comments, 1990-1993. (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Comments, 1991-1993. (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Comments, 1992-1993. (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Conflict of Interest Reports, 1990. (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Conflict of Interest Reports, 1991. (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Conflict of Interest Reports, 1992. (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Conflict of Interest Reports, 1993. (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Constituent Office, 1991. (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Correspondence, 1990. (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Honorary Chairman, 1990-1991. (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Interview Requests, 1991-1993. (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Interview Requests, 1992-1994. (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Interview Requests, 1993-1994. (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Interview Requests--Accepted, 1991-1993. (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Interview Requests--Accepted, 1991-1993. (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Interview Requests--Accepted, 1991-1993. (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Interview Requests--Accepted, 1991-1993. (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Interview Requests--Accepted, 1991-1993. (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Interview Requests--Declined, 1991-1993. (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Interview Requests--Declined, 1991-1993. (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Interview Requests--Declined, 1991-1993. (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Interview Requests--Declined, 1991-1993. (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Interview Requests--Declined, 1991-1993. (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Interview Requests--Declined, 1991-1993. (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Invitations 1-8 November, 1989. (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Invitations 8-14 November, 1989. (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Invitations 15-21 November, 1989. (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Invitations 22-28 November, 1989. (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Invitations 29-30 November, 1989. (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Invitations December, 1989. (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Invitations December, 1989. (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Invitations 8-14 December, 1989. (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Invitations 8-14 December, 1989. (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Invitations 15-21 December, 1989. (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Invitations 22-28 December, 1989. (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Invitations 22-28 December, 1989. (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Invitations 1-7 January, 1990. (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Invitations 8-14 January, 1990. (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Invitations 15-21 January, 1990. (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Invitations 22-31 January, 1990. (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Invitations 1-8 February, 1990. (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Invitations 9-16 February, 1990. (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Invitations 17-24 February, 1990. (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Invitations 25-28 February, 1990. (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Invitations 1-8 March, 1990. (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Invitations 9-16 March, 1990. (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Invitations 17-24 March, 1990. (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Invitations 25-31 March, 1990. (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Invitations 1-8 April, 1990. (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Invitations 17-24 April, 1990. (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Invitations 17-24 April, 1990. (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Invitations 25-30 April, 1990. (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Invitations 1-8 May, 1990. (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Invitations 9-16 May, 1990. (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Invitations 17-24 May, 1990. (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Invitations 25-31 May, 1990. (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Invitations June, 1990. (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Invitations August, 1990. (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Invitations September, 1990. (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Invitations October, 1990. (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Invitations November, 1990. (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Invitations January, 1991. (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Invitations November, 1991. (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Invitations 1-5 December, 1991. (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Invitations 6-8 December, 1991. (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Invitations 9-13 December, 1991. (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Invitations 14-29 December, 1991. (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Invitations 1-10 January, 1992. (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Invitations 11-16 January, 1992. (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Invitations 17-22 January, 1992. (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Invitations 23-31 January, 1992. (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Invitations 1 February, 1992. (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Invitations 2-5 February, 1992. (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Invitations 6-14 February, 1992. (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Invitations 15-19 February, 1992. (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Invitations 20-22 February, 1992. (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Invitations 23-29 February, 1992. (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Invitations 1-6 March, 1992. (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Invitations 7-15 March, 1992. (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Invitations 16-20 March, 1992. (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Invitations 21-26 March, 1992. (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Invitations 27-31 March, 1992. (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Invitations 1-4 April, 1992. (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Invitations 5-7 April, 1992. (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Invitations 8-10 April, 1992. (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Invitations 11-14 April, 1992. (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Invitations 16-24 April, 1992. (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Invitations 25-30 April, 1992. (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Invitations 1-3 May, 1992. (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Invitations 4-8 May, 1992. (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Invitations 9-14 May, 1992. (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Invitations 15-17 May, 1992. (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Invitations 18-21 May, 1992. (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Invitations 22-27 May, 1992. (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Invitations 28-31 May, 1992. (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Invitations 1-4 June, 1992. (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Invitations 5-8 June, 1992. (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Invitations 9-14 June, 1992. (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Invitations 15-24 June, 1992. (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Invitations 25-30 June, 1992. (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Invitations 1-8 October, 1992. (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Invitations 9-14 October, 1992. (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Invitations 1-3 April, 1993. (Box 18, Folder 2)
- Invitations 4-7 April, 1993. (Box 18, Folder 3)
- Invitations 8-15 April, 1993. (Box 18, Folder 4)
- Invitations 16-19 April, 1993. (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Invitations 20-22 April, 1993. (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Invitations 22-24 April, 1993. (Box 18, Folder 7)
- Invitations 25-27 April, 1993. (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Invitations 27-30 April, 1993. (Box 19, Folder 2)
- Invitations 1-6 May, 1993. (Box 19, Folder 3)
- Invitations 6-9 May, 1993. (Box 19, Folder 4)
- Invitations 10-14 May, 1993. (Box 19, Folder 5)
- Invitations 15-19 May, 1993. (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Invitations 20-23 May, 1993. (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Invitations 23-31 May, 1993. (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Invitations 1-3 June, 1993. (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Invitations 4-9 June, 1993. (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Invitations 10-14 June, 1993. (Box 21, Folder 2)
- Invitations 15-21 June, 1993. (Box 21, Folder 3)
- Invitations 22-30 June, 1993. (Box 21, Folder 4)
- Invitations 1-7 July, 1993. (Box 22, Folder 1)
- Invitations 8-15 July, 1993. (Box 22, Folder 2)
- Invitations 16-25 July, 1993. (Box 22, Folder 3)
- Invitations 26-31 July, 1993. (Box 22, Folder 4)
- Invitations 1-6 August, 1993. (Box 22, Folder 5)
- Invitations 7-14 August, 1993. (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Invitations 15-23 August, 1993. (Box 23, Folder 2)
- Invitations 24-31 August, 1993. (Box 23, Folder 3)
- Invitations 1-9 September, 1993. (Box 23, Folder 4)
- Invitations 10-15 September, 1993. (Box 23, Folder 5)
- Invitations 16-18 September, 1993. (Box 24, Folder 1)
- Invitations 19-20 September, 1993. (Box 24, Folder 2)
- Invitations 21-25 September, 1993. (Box 24, Folder 3)
- Invitations 26-30 September, 1993. (Box 24, Folder 4)
- Invitations 1-4 October, 1993. (Box 24, Folder 5)
- Invitations 5-12 October, 1993. (Box 25, Folder 1)
- Invitations 13-17 October, 1993. (Box 25, Folder 2)
- Invitations 18-23 October, 1993. (Box 25, Folder 3)
- Invitations 24-31 October, 1993. (Box 25, Folder 4)
- Invitations 1-10 November, 1993. (Box 25, Folder 5)
- Invitations 11-17 November, 1993. (Box 26, Folder 1)
- Invitations 18-30 November, 1993. (Box 26, Folder 2)
- Invitations 1-8 December, 1993. (Box 26, Folder 3)
- Invitations 9-13 December, 1993. (Box 26, Folder 4)
- Invitations, 1993. (Box 27, Folder 1)
- Invitations, 1993. (Box 27, Folder 2)
- Invitations, 1993. (Box 27, Folder 3)
- Invitations, 1993. (Box 27, Folder 4)
- Invitations, 1993. (Box 27, Folder 5)
- Invitations--Backups, 1990. (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Invitations--Black History Month, 1991. (Box 28, Folder 2)
- Invitations--Black History Month, 1991. (Box 28, Folder 3)
- Invitations--Black History Month, 1991-1992. (Box 28, Folder 4)
- Invitations--Chicago Unity Dinner, 1990. (Box 28, Folder 5)
- Invitations--Commencements, 1989. (Box 28, Folder 6)
- Invitations--Commencements, 1990-1991. (Box 29, Folder 1)
- Invitations--Declines, 1989-1990. (Box 29, Folder 2)
- Invitations--General Correspondence November, 1989. (Box 29, Folder 3)
- Invitations--Graduations, 1990-1991. (Box 29, Folder 4)
- Invitations--King, Martin Luther, Jr. Day Events, 1990-1992. (Box 29, Folder 5)
- Invitations--King, Martin Luther, Jr. Day Events, 1991. (Box 29, Folder 6)
- Invitations--National Governor's Association, 1990. (Box 30, Folder 1)
- Invitations--National Political, 1990-1991. (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Invitations--Open, 1989. (Box 30, Folder 3)
- Invitations--Open/Declines, 1989. (Box 30, Folder 4)
- Invitations--Post Election Regrets, 1989. (Box 30, Folder 5)
- Invitations--Post Election Regrets, 1989. (Box 30, Folder 6)
- Invitations--Schools, 1990-1991. (Box 30, Folder 7)
- Invitations--Virginia Democratic Party, 1990-1991. (Box 30, Folder 8)
- Invoices, 1990. (Box 30, Folder 9)
- Invoices, 1991. (Box 31, Folder 1)
- Invoices, 1992. (Box 31, Folder 2)
- Invoices, 1993. (Box 31, Folder 3)
- Legislative Liaison Office, 1990-1991. (Box 31, Folder 4)
- Mansion, 1990. (Box 31, Folder 5)
- Maupin, Nancy, 1990-1991. (Box 31, Folder 6)
- Memoranda--Miscellaneous, 1989-1993. (Box 31, Folder 7)
- Memoranda--Miscellaneous, 1990. (Box 31, Folder 8)
- Memoranda--Miscellaneous, 1990. (Box 32, Folder 1)
- Non-Scheduling Miscellaneous, 1990-1991. (Box 32, Folder 2)
- Northern, Bill, 1990-1991. (Box 32, Folder 3)
- Photographs, 1990. (Box 32, Folder 4)
- Porter, Bill, 1991. (Box 32, Folder 5)
- Regrets 1-3 January, 1991. (Box 32, Folder 6)
- Regrets 4 January, 1991. (Box 32, Folder 7)
- Regrets 6-15 January, 1991. (Box 32, Folder 8)
- Regrets 16-24 January, 1991. (Box 33, Folder 1)
- Regrets 25-31, 1991. (Box 33, Folder 2)
- Regrets 1-2 February, 1991. (Box 33, Folder 3)
- Regrets 3-7 February, 1991. (Box 33, Folder 4)
- Regrets 8-15 February, 1991. (Box 33, Folder 5)
- Regrets 16-24 February, 1991. (Box 33, Folder 6)
- Regrets 25-28 February, 1991. (Box 33, Folder 7)
- Regrets 1-5 March, 1991. (Box 34, Folder 1)
- Regrets 6-10 March, 1991. (Box 34, Folder 2)
- Regrets 11-14 March, 1991. (Box 34, Folder 3)
- Regrets 15-20 March, 1991. (Box 34, Folder 4)
- Regrets 21-23 March, 1991. (Box 34, Folder 5)
- Regrets 24-31 March, 1991. (Box 34, Folder 6)
- Regrets 1-5 April, 1991. (Box 35, Folder 1)
- Regrets 6-7 April, 1991. (Box 35, Folder 2)
- Regrets 8-10 April, 1991. (Box 35, Folder 3)
- Regrets 11-14 April, 1991. (Box 35, Folder 4)
- Regrets 15-18 April, 1991. (Box 35, Folder 5)
- Regrets 18 April, 1991. (Box 35, Folder 6)
- Regrets 19-20 April, 1991. (Box 36, Folder 1)
- Regrets 20-22 April, 1991. (Box 36, Folder 2)
- Regrets 23-25 April, 1991. (Box 36, Folder 3)
- Regrets 26 April, 1991. (Box 36, Folder 4)
- Regrets 27-30 April, 1991. (Box 36, Folder 5)
- Regrets 1-2 May, 1991. (Box 36, Folder 6)
- Regrets 2-6 May, 1991. (Box 37, Folder 1)
- Regrets 6-10 May, 1991. (Box 37, Folder 2)
- Regrets 11-15 May, 1991. (Box 37, Folder 3)
- Regrets 16-18 May, 1991. (Box 37, Folder 4)
- Regrets 19-22 May, 1991. (Box 37, Folder 5)
- Regrets 23-24 May, 1991. (Box 38, Folder 1)
- Regrets 25-31 May, 1991. (Box 38, Folder 2)
- Regrets 1 June, 1991. (Box 38, Folder 3)
- Regrets 2-7 June, 1991. (Box 38, Folder 4)
- Regrets 8-10 June, 1991. (Box 38, Folder 5)
- Regrets 10 June, 1991. (Box 38, Folder 6)
- Regrets 11-14 June, 1991. (Box 39, Folder 1)
- Regrets 15-18 June, 1991. (Box 39, Folder 2)
- Regrets 19-21 June, 1991. (Box 39, Folder 3)
- Regrets 22-24 June, 1991. (Box 39, Folder 4)
- Regrets 25-28 June, 1991. (Box 39, Folder 5)
- Regrets 29-30 June, 1991. (Box 40, Folder 1)
- Regrets 1-6 July, 1991. (Box 40, Folder 2)
- Regrets 7-14 July, 1991. (Box 40, Folder 3)
- Regrets 15-19 July, 1991. (Box 40, Folder 4)
- Regrets 20-24 July, 1991. (Box 40, Folder 5)
- Regrets 25-31 July, 1991. (Box 40, Folder 6)
- Regrets 1-2 August, 1991. (Box 41, Folder 1)
- Regrets 3-14 August, 1991. (Box 41, Folder 2)
- Regrets 15-24 August, 1991. (Box 41, Folder 3)
- Regrets 25-27 August, 1991. (Box 41, Folder 4)
- Regrets 28-31 August, 1991. (Box 41, Folder 5)
- Regrets 1-6 September, 1991. (Box 42, Folder 1)
- Regrets 7-12 September, 1991. (Box 42, Folder 2)
- Regrets 13-17 September, 1991. (Box 42, Folder 3)
- Regrets 18-20 September, 1991. (Box 42, Folder 4)
- Regrets 21-23 September, 1991. (Box 42, Folder 5)
- Regrets 24-27 September, 1991. (Box 42, Folder 6)
- Regrets 28-30 September, 1991. (Box 43, Folder 1)
- Regrets 1 October, 1991. (Box 43, Folder 2)
- Regrets 2-9 October, 1991. (Box 43, Folder 3)
- Regrets 10-11 October, 1991. (Box 43, Folder 4)
- Regrets 12-14 October, 1991. (Box 43, Folder 5)
- Regrets 15-18 October, 1991. (Box 44, Folder 1)
- Regrets 19-23 October, 1991. (Box 44, Folder 2)
- Regrets 24 October, 1991. (Box 44, Folder 3)
- Regrets 24-25 October, 1991. (Box 44, Folder 4)
- Regrets 26-31 October, 1991. (Box 44, Folder 5)
- Regrets--Associations, 1990-1991. (Box 45, Folder 1)
- Regrets--Associations, 1990-1991. (Box 45, Folder 2)
- Regrets--Associations, 1990-1991. (Box 45, Folder 3)
- Regrets--Associations, 1991. (Box 45, Folder 4)
- Regrets--Associations, 1991. (Box 45, Folder 5)
- Regrets--Associations, 1991. (Box 46, Folder 1)
- Regrets--Associations, 1991. (Box 46, Folder 2)
- Regrets--Associations, 1991. (Box 46, Folder 3)
- Regrets--Associations, 1991. (Box 46, Folder 4)
- Regrets--Associations, 1991. (Box 46, Folder 5)
- Regrets--House of Delegates, 1990-1991. (Box 46, Folder 6)
- Regrets--Individuals Miscellaneous, 1991. (Box 47, Folder 1)
- Regrets--Mansion, 1990. (Box 47, Folder 2)
- Regrets--Schools, 1990-1991. (Box 47, Folder 3)
- Regrets--Schools, 1990-1991. (Box 47, Folder 4)
- Regrets--Senators, 1990-1991. (Box 47, Folder 5)
- Requests--Group Miscellaneous, 1993. (Box 47, Folder 6)
- Requests--Individual Miscellaneous, 1993. (Box 47, Folder 7)
- Requests--Individual Miscellaneous, 1993. (Box 48, Folder 1)
- Secretary of Administration, 1990-1991. (Box 48, Folder 2)
- Secretary of Economic Development, 1990. (Box 48, Folder 3)
- Secretary of Economic Development, 1990-1991. (Box 48, Folder 4)
- Secretary of Economic Development, 1990-1991. (Box 48, Folder 5)
- Secretary of Economic Development, 1990-1991. (Box 48, Folder 6)
- Secretary of Economic Development, 1990-1991. (Box 48, Folder 7)
- Secretary of Education, 1990-1991. (Box 49, Folder 1)
- Secretary of Education, 1990-1992. (Box 49, Folder 2)
- Secretary of Finance, 1990-1991. (Box 49, Folder 3)
- Secretary of Health and Human Resources, 1990-1991. (Box 49, Folder 4)
- Secretary of Natural Resources, 1990-1991. (Box 49, Folder 5)
- Secretary of Public Safety, 1990-1991. (Box 49, Folder 6)
- Secretary of Transportation, 1989-1991. (Box 49, Folder 7)
- Schedules, 1991-1994. (Box 50, Folder 1)
- Schedules 14 October-15 December, 1992. (Box 50, Folder 2)
- Schedules 4-28 January, 1993. (Box 50, Folder 3)
- Schedules 1-25 February, 1993. (Box 50, Folder 4)
- Schedules 1-31 March, 1993. (Box 50, Folder 5)
- Schedules 2-29 April, 1993. (Box 50, Folder 6)
- Schedules 4-12 May, 1993. (Box 50, Folder 7)
- Schedules Memos, 1989. (Box 50, Folder 8)
- Shropshire, J. T., 1990. (Box 50, Folder 9)
- Southern States Energy Board, 1990. (Box 50, Folder 10)
- Thank You's, 1990-1991. (Box 50, Folder 11)
- Welcome Home Troops, 1991. (Box 50, Folder 12)